[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Mercedes] The police raided
Club Dragonfly.
They were able to arrest our staff,
confiscate all our profits,
and close down the club.
[Helena] Tell our connections
in the police force
to make sure your name isn't linked
to the club in any way.
[Anna] How can we trust you
when you're keeping secrets from us?
Do we still have your loyalty,
or is it with her?
Anna, you are my family.
You, Lily… We're family.
What kind of question is that?
You're hiding something from me.
I know you've met your mother.
[Apollo] Madam, have mercy on me.
[Helena] That's what I want to do
to my new enemies.
Because fire melts gold.
I want to burn Lily Cruz alive!
[Damian] You have no idea
how vicious your enemies are.
But I'm here.
I will protect you from Red Dragon,
even if it kills me.
[Mercedes] Can we still trust Jaguar?
He might betray us because
our enemies are related to him.
I don't trust him at all.
Let me introduce you.
Lily Cruz, meet Helena Montoya,
CEO of Montoya Industries.
It's nice to meet you.
[Lily] Poblacion Ardiente needs
people like you.
What are you proposing?
I'm going to have a charity event
to kick-start Oplan Restore
Poblacion Ardiente.
[Jose] You have a visitor.
I'm back. Well and alive.
The time has come for you
to know the whole truth.
You liar! You cheated on me!
No! Please! I'm pregnant.
-[gunshot]
-[Helena] He killed my father
and separated us.
The time has come for my revenge.
[Julio] Those who play with fire,
with Julio Ardiente, will burn!
Just because I'm no longer governor,
doesn't mean it's the end of all
our business transactions!
Remember that!
Everyone, get out.
I said, everyone, get out!
Sanggano, leave us.
My dearest Papa, you and I
have a lot to talk about.
You took me away from my real mother
and made her think I was dead.
How could you do that?!
Emilia, my dear, please don't
exaggerate your stories.
You act as if I treated you like garbage.
If I had, you would've been
abandoned in some dumpster!
But you never treated me
like your daughter!
You even love Arnaldo
more than you love me.
[laughs]
So now you're jealous of your own son?!
See?! See how much of a brat you are?
Let's get one thing clear.
I never treated you indifferently.
I never abused you!
I let you live in a palace.
I provided you with the best education
money could buy!
I gave you everything.
I even gave you governorship
of this province
once upon a time!
Yes. You're right, Papa.
You gave me everything.
But you never gave me the chance
to be with my real mother,
and nothing can replace that!
But she found me, she never gave up on me!
And that's what real love is. Unlike you!
You are so selfish, Papa.
And now that she's found me,
she's going to make me queen.
And nothing can stop that,
not even you, the great Julio Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
Your mother was a harlot!
Darn!
[exhales]
Emilia, wait.
What now?!
What was that I heard you and your dad
were talking about downstairs?
About your real mother?
Grab a newspaper,
and get with the program.
Emilia, that's why I'm asking you.
So, why don't you just tell me
about these things,
instead of telling other people?!
Well, you can't really blame me, Raul.
It's much easier
talking to others than you.
Hold on, Emilia.
Why do you always
have to walk out when we fight?
Can't we just talk like husband and wife?
What's there to talk about?
Don't you plan to introduce me to Mommy?
[scoffs] Mommy?!
Why don't you go prove your worth first?
I don't want you making a fool out of me!
And, by the way, you aren't
invited to the event, okay?
So, go do something else.
Like, go to the gym, or whatever.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Mama?
[Helena] Hello, Emilia, darling.
So, have you spoken to your father?
Yes, Mama. He's still
the same old, prideful man,
with no hint of regret
for all the mistakes he's done.
You know, I don't think
he's ever going to change.
Well, you have to be patient,
my dear. Remember…
we can still use him.
I want him to attend the charity event
so I can show him
how the pros get it done.
Wait, Mama. Are you gonna give me a hint
on what's about to happen?
Well, let's just say that…
I'm going to blind the people
of Ardiente with diamonds.
Diamonds?
Yes, I'm going to donate 20
million pesos worth of diamonds
to the people of Ardiente.
[laughs] Twenty million pesos
worth of diamonds?
Wow. That's a lot, Mama.
I'm so excited to go to that event.
I can't wait to see you there.
-Bye.
-See you.
Hmm… Twenty million pesos
worth of diamonds.
Wow.
Lily.
Mom.
Lily, are you sure we're going
to that Helena Montoya's charity event?
We have to, Mom.
But what if it's just a trap?
I've already beefed up security.
I won't let any of us get hurt
at that charity event.
But we have to go there
so I can find out
who Helena Montoya really is.
There, we'll find out her true identity.
And that's when I'll find out
whether she's my enemy
or my ally.
[suspenseful music playing]
[waltz music playing]
[music fading]
Get ready because we have another mission.
A certain package will arrive
at Helena Montoya's charity event.
Diamonds worth 20 million pesos.
But it won't reach the charity event
because we'll take them all.
Understood?
Understood, Boss Jaguar.
Oh, Jaguar. You're not late.
You're on time, huh? [chuckles]
I have a job for you. Get your men ready.
Protect the diamonds
I've sent for the charity event.
Make sure that they get there.
[distorted voice]
As you wish, Madam Red Dragon.
Very good.
[suspenseful music playing]
[waltz music playing]
-This way, please.
-Thank you.
We should stay here.
[waltz music playing]
They're here.
[suspenseful music playing]
-[usherette] This way, ma'am.
-Okay.
Excuse me, ma'am. Name, please.
My name's Natalie.
Surname?
Well, about that.
I actually invited myself.
I'm sure there's nothing wrong with that.
I want to meet the wealthiest jeweler
in all of Southeast Asia.
Can you make it happen?
I'm sorry, ma'am, but this event
is strictly by invitation.
[chuckles]
Darling, why don't you do both
of us a favor and let me in.
I'm a VIP, you know.
-VIP?!
-I'm sorry, ma'am,
-[laughs]
-but you have to leave.
You're so right, you're a VIP.
Very immoral person.
[laughs] That's so witty. I like it a lot!
And guess what? It suits you too.
Because it takes one to know one.
Emilia, look at me.
I'm not in a chair,
and I'm not tied to it.
Which means it's payback time.
Enough of these confrontation scenes.
I'm sick of them!
-[grunts]
-Oops! Not too fast.
Come on. Take her out. Pronto.
-[Natalie] Let me go! Hey!
-Crazy.
[grunts]
[Natalie] Let me go!
[tense music playing]
Hmm!
If it isn't Ivy Aguas.
Or is it Lily Cruz?
[sighs] I'm so confused. Who are you?
But all I know is you, little witch,
are invited to this party.
But don't you worry
because I will deal with the other witch.
Really?
[laughs] Yes. I will deal with you.
One, two, three. It's a reunion!
This is so fun.
I'm going to have so much fun
with these three little witches.
Let me deal with that witch.
Wow.
Apparently, it slipped her mind
that I haven't forgotten
that she buried me alive.
Lily Cruz, why are you
wearing green and not gold?
What happened to that gold outfit?
[laughs]
Oh, no. Has Lily Cruz lost her luster?
You know what, Emilia?
They say gold glitters.
But not all that glitters is gold.
I am gold.
But you, and you…
Just look at yourselves.
I'd say you're just copper.
I don't even know what that is.
You shut up.
But in all fairness to you, Natalie,
no matter where you are in Ardiente,
you're always in the know.
Lily Cruz? Ivy Aguas?
They are the same person.
And that's me.
Well, I've no time for chatting
with people like you.
And you, Emilia…
Starting today,
you should fear for your life.
Because not only will I bury you alive,
I'll make your life a living hell.
[chuckles]
For now, maybe.
But in a while,
I'll make you wish you had never
left your old casket, Lily Cruz.
[laughing]
You may have tried to bury us
both back then,
but what else should we expect
from a she-demon like you?
[laughing]
-Wait. Wow!
-[Natalie laughing]
There are now four witches.
One, two, three, four.
The more the merrier. I love it.
I love it! This is gonna be so exciting!
We're gonna fight,
-and I'll pull your hair.
-Hey, you.
-And your hair.
-And why are you laughing, huh?
You think I don't know why you're here?
You're here to seduce
my husband again, aren't you?
[laughs] That's so last month.
I've moved on.
I've squeezed everything
I needed out of your husband.
I mean, information, that is.
So, now, who could my new flavor
of the month be?
Or should I address that to you?
Wanna take a guess, Lily Cruz?
Take a wild guess.
Who cares?
[laughing]
-[laughs]
-Hmm…
[Natalie] I'm so confused.
You might go crazy when you find out who.
Lily Cruz!
[tense music playing]
[Natalie laughs]
You can turn your backs on me.
I don't really care 'cause
none of you can take me on.
Especially not you.
Because you're a sore loser,
Emilia! Loser!
-Really?
-Yes.
Girls, please escort this little birdbrain
out of here.
-I can walk! What?!
-And do her a good job.
-[woman] Good job?
-Yes. Kill her!
You're such a loser, Emilia!
[laughs] I'll see you in hell. Take care.
[Natalie] Let me go!
-Oh! I love it!
-[Natalie grunts]
[jazz music playing]
[Lily] Anna.
[host] May I request everyone
to please settle down?
[jazz music playing]
[groans]
Hi, Lily Cruz, my favorite adversary.
How are you?
So, are you ready to compete against me
in earning Helena Montoya's favor?
[chuckles]
Emilia, I don't need
to compete against you.
Did you honestly forget?
I already beat you.
And I don't want to make a scene
because I came here
to create ties with Helena
for Ardiente's citizens.
So, please.
So, you honestly believe
that Helena Montoya
wants a partnership with you?
Pretty cocky, aren't you?
Anyway, everything will
be revealed tonight,
although it might be too much for you.
Your jaw might just drop.
Try me.
Careful with that.
Just follow them.
[Helena] Thank you all very much
for coming.
Thank you very much.
I would especially like
to thank Lily Cruz…
for coming this evening
and supporting this event.
-Thank you, Lily.
-[mouths] You're welcome.
I bet many of you are wondering
why I chose to help Poblacion Ardiente,
of all places.
But many of you don't know that
I have memories of this place,
which is why I chose
to build a better future here.
Poblacion Ardiente is my home.
Because my family lives here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I would like to introduce to you
my long-lost daughter…
[tense music playing]
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[applause]
Mama.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[applause]
-[soft music playing]
-I love you, Mama.
-I love you, baby girl.
To those of you asking,
"How did this happen?"
Oh, it's such a long story.
We don't have the whole night.
But as you all know,
I endeavor to empower women and mothers.
And for the longest time,
I have been a champion of mothers.
But what most of you might not know…
is that I'm also a mother
who's been looking for her child
for so long.
But that all ends here tonight.
Today, I am proud to announce
that I am finally reunited
with my beloved daughter.
And no one, not even the demon himself,
can tear us apart.
I love you, Mama.
I love you, baby girl.
Once again, the philanthropist,
the successful businesswoman…
Hail to the queen. Helena Montoya!
[applause]
-[applause]
-[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Get that away from me.
I think I might steal it.
An egg.
That's how big your brain is.
As big as a quail egg!
Do you want Red Dragon
to cut off your fingers?
We were ordered to deliver
and protect her diamonds.
Only an idiot would betray Red Dragon.
Boss, someone's following us.
Boss, looks like we have company.
We do.
The fake Jaguar.
Step on it, buzz-cut.
[distorted voice] Faster. Hurry.
I said, faster!
[tires screeching]
Get ready.
-[gunshots]
-[tires screeching]
[Damian] Get down.
[suspenseful music playing]
Give us the diamonds,
and we promise we'll let you pass.
[softly] You've got a screw loose.
These are Red Dragon's diamonds.
Blood will be spilled
before I give these to you.
[suspenseful music playing]
All right then.
[gunshots]
[Damian] Retreat!
[Raul] Check it out!
[Raul] Corner them!
[Raul] Grab the diamonds! Quick!
[Raul] Give me that thing! Give it here!
[Damian] Hey!
[explosion]
[Raul groaning]
[Damian] Get those creaky bodies moving
if you don't want to be beaten,
stop sleeping there like helpless kittens!
Hey, that rhymed!
[laughs mockingly]
I'm a poet!
Get the diamond.
[grunts]
[grunts, groans]
[groans]
[Raul] Quit acting like you're all that.
You're just another lackey!
[Damian laughs mockingly]
Why don't you look at yourself,
little kitten?
Fake little Jaguar here became a has-been.
Too bad!
You better practice first,
if you want to get a punch in!
[laughs mockingly]
It still rhymed! Come on, boys!
[suspenseful music playing]
[engine turns over]
[Helena] And now,
let's go to the main event.
[suspenseful music playing]
I would like to present
my biggest diamond collection.
The Phoenix! For Poblacion Ardiente.
-[applause]
-[tense music playing]
[eerie music]
So Emilia is Helena Montoya's daughter?
[Mr. Castro] Miss Cruz.
We need to set a meeting with you
and Mrs. Helena Montoya.
She's the CEO of Montoya Industries.
She made a great offer.
[Mateo] She's the most successful jeweler
in the Philippines, and she's
willing to share her fortunes
with the people of Ardiente.
[Lily] The same Helena Montoya
who wants to invest in my company.
That's me.
Let's help each other.
Together, we can help
the people of Ardiente
rise from the ashes.
Now I know why she wants
to get close to me.
She's planning something against you.
It's obvious, Diego.
But what Helena's doing?
She's taking a page from Ivy Aguas' book.
I want to be part of Ardiente's progress.
An auction whose profits will go
to the campaign fund
of our congressman.
I hope this is the start
of our partnership.
For Poblacion Ardiente! Cheers!
She has no originality.
But, oh well…
If that's what she wants,
the show must go on.
[tense music playing]
Helena, I love your whole collection.
Thank you.
But aren't they all
too precious to be donated?
Precious diamonds for this precious town?
Only my new hometown deserves the best.
See? That's my Mama. Isn't she nice?
And she can fund it,
unlike you and Diego Torillo's project.
You'll only pale in comparison.
[clears throat]
Oh, Helena, don't mind your daughter.
She's always been like that.
So, please be patient with her.
But as for me,
I will never compete with you. Never.
Lily, please believe me when I say
I only have good intentions for this town.
As a matter of fact,
I've already thought of
so many projects.
Why don't you join me
in my latest project for the town?
Sure, Helena. Sure.
This conversation stinks.
Excuse me?
Well, you know, I must admit,
you both are very good actresses.
To be able to stand each other
and not get at each other's throats?
My, I'll give you an A for effort.
Although as much as I hate the guts
of this woman in green, she's right.
Those diamonds are only beautiful
to a fool who thinks
they don't come with a price.
You're staging a comeback, Helena.
And you want to take over my town?
[chuckles, tutting]
Julio.
I truly want to help this town, yes.
But I won't force you.
Because only a fool thinks
that he can change the mind
of another fool.
[Julio] Wow. She thinks.
Why don't we all raise our glasses?
After all, we all want
the best for our town.
-[Emilia] Yeah.
-[taps on glass]
Onward, Ardiente!
Um, Mama, it's Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
-Nice!
[Mateo] Viva Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[soft music playing]
[Jepoy] I'll go with you.
[Anna] Why?
Doesn't your girl need you now?
[Jepoy] First of all,
Natalie's not my girl.
Second…
I'll go with you to protect you.
Please believe me.
I'll prove that you have my loyalty.
[line ringing]
Anna. Where's Jepoy?
He suddenly left, Auntie Camia.
I'm trying to call him,
but he won't answer.
I don't know where he went.
-[line ringing]
-[suspenseful music playing]
Let me go! [grunts]
Why are you two so strong?!
You're so tiny!
[grunts]
[shrieks, whimpers]
What kind of trick is that?
It's so tacky!
-Are you guys crazy?
-This isn't a trick!
This is what will burn you alive!
Madam Emilia says goodbye.
What does that wretch even think she is?!
[shrieks, whimpers]
Is this a circus? Are we at a festival?
Can you just stop this nonsense?!
What's that?
Uh, excuse me!
[panting] No!
[breathing raggedly]
Stop it!
Can you stop?! [shrieks]
Stop! Ugh!
How do you even swallow this?!
This is disgusting!
[suspenseful music playing]
-Hey, let her go!
-Madrigal!
Whoa!
-[henchwoman screams]
-[Jepoy, henchwomen grunting]
I'm serious!
Let her go!
Ladies first, I guess.
-[screams]
-[grunts]
[screams]
[grunting, groaning]
Back off!
-Yay!
-Ma'am!
Madrigal, thank you so much!
[Jepoy] Why did you crash
the event in the first place?
Are you crazy?!
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
I knew you'd save me.
[squeals]
[grunts]
Thank you.
[squeals]
You're lucky I found you.
[smooches]
-Thank you.
[Emilia scoffs]
The next time you cross over my Mama,
I will crush you like a fly.
[exhales]
Go ahead, Emilia.
You know what?
All you do is bark and bark.
But you keep hiding behind
your mother's skirt
because you can't handle me.
You and I are mortal enemies.
And you know that.
You also know that when a child
sees their mother hurt,
they'll do something about it.
So, keep my mother out of this. Okay?
Because no one's been declared the victor
in our fight yet. Get that?
Just accept it, Emilia.
Accept your loss, Emilia.
Because I already won.
And don't worry.
I won't drag your mother into this.
But, please, don't get jealous.
Because I already feel a sense
of connection with your mother.
I just know we're going to be close.
Excuse me.
Hmm!
You witch!
[tense music playing]
Hmm.
Lily, I don't trust that Helena.
Who would give away diamonds
just like that?
If she just wanted to be with Emilia…
she didn't have to make a grand show
announcing the whole thing.
She's doing all this to get close to you.
All I'm going to do with Helena…
is dance to her tune.
But Lily…
Be wary.
You don't know who you're up against.
Protect yourself. Don't level with her.
Mom, my plan is to wait and see
just what she'll do to me.
They may have buried Ivy Aguas,
but her words still remain.
So to Emilia and Helena… don't try me.
[suspenseful music playing]
Why did you have to make a scene?
Aren't you smarter than that?
And no mother would let a lunatic like you
hurt their child!
You're lucky I was there.
If you'll just rub it
in my face that you saved me,
I wish you didn't even save me anymore!
I don't need you! I can manage!
Try telling yourself that!
If I didn't come…
Then what?
I already saved you before.
And thank you for saving me!
Now, we're even!
Now, you can just go!
Why don't you just go and leave me?!
Leave!
What are you staring at?!
Ma'am…
just be careful.
I don't want this happening again.
[gasps]
I had so much fun tonight, Mama.
I love that on you. It's so beautiful.
Thank you.
Now, that move was low
even for you, Helena.
[sighs]
Which one? The diamonds I gave to charity?
The ones you gave me months
before you left me,
and took away my daughter?
Julio, it's just a constant reminder
of the monster that you are
and will always be.
So what?
You returned to reunite
with your long-lost daughter to spite me?
I'm not here for
petty sentimentalities, Julio.
I'm here to help my daughter
achieve her ambitions.
You use your force, and I use my charm.
[scoffs]
And my charm is going to cloak
the violent force
that's gonna annihilate my enemy.
You're in luck.
We share the same enemy.
So, why don't you just sit back and relax,
and watch me bleed Lily Cruz to death?
[speaking in Spanish] The enemy
of my enemy is my friend.
-Bye.
-Bye, Mama.
[scoffs]
Your mother hasn't changed one bit.
She's still the feisty woman I knew.
Man-eater, destroyer, firecracker.
[clicks tongue]
You know, Papa, I can see in your eyes
that you're head
over heels crazy about Mama.
Look at those eyes.
Twinkling.
But eat her dust!
Did you see how she looked at me?
[Emilia humming]
As thick as oil.
Go and join your new master.
[laughs]
I am going to enjoy this.
[upbeat music playing]
[art dealer] It's the same, actually.
Miss Montoya follows a certain rate.
So, there's a price ceiling.
So, we can't just…
Sir, excuse me, please.
Hi, ma'am. Good morning.
This installation is made
of precious stones
like jade, diamond, and amethyst.
A personal offer of Miss Montoya.
It's beautiful.
But isn't Mrs. Montoya a jewelry maker?
Well, she also creates mixed media arts
featuring women rising from tragedies,
metamorphosis, blossoming flowers…
butterflies, and phoenixes,
as you can see in the installation.
I'll get that and this one.
And I want to send a note to Miss Montoya.
Sure, ma'am.
Oh, um, would you know
where I can find her?
[suspenseful music playing]
[piano music playing]
Paula, make an appointment
for Mrs. Harper.
Tell her that she needs to fit her tiara.
Madam, someone wants to talk to you.
I don't have an appointment today.
[Paula] Um, ma'am.
[tense music playing]
[Paula] Excuse me.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Helena] If you loathe them,
why are you here?
Am I now your enemy too?
Or is it because
you're planning to use me?
Is that also why you haven't
declared war against me, Helena?
[Mercedes] Have you started?
Or should I just kill you
together with Camia and Lily?
Helena Montoya is somehow
connected to Mercedes Palacio.
How can there be a reunion
when my grandson isn't here?
Let me go! Let me go!
[Helena] Diego is a thorn.
So if you don't do something
about it tonight,
then you are the biggest thorn
in this family!
[theme music playing]